[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What was the publication Kubrick was a photographer for?",
        "options": ["People", "Life", "Look", "The New Yorker"],
        "correctAnswer": "Look"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Where in England did Kubrick live?",
        "options": ["York", "Oxford", "Childwickbury", "London"],
        "correctAnswer": "Childwickbury"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What was Kubrick first feature film?",
        "options": ["Fear and Desire", "The Killing", "Killer's Kiss", "Paths of Glory"],
        "correctAnswer": "Fear and Desire"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is the title of the book The Killing is based on?",
        "options": ["What's the Point?", "The Track Job", "Race Heist", "Clean Break"],
        "correctAnswer": "Clean Break"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What horror film was Stanley offered to direct?",
        "options": ["The Exorcist", "Last House on the Left", "Alien", "Carrie"],
        "correctAnswer": "The Exorcist"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which director sent a fan letter to Kubrick that meant so much to Kubrick, he took so long to write a response that the director died before receiving the response?",
        "options": ["Ingmar Bergman", "Federico Fellini", "Akira Kurosawa", "Andrei Tarkovsky"],
        "correctAnswer": "Akira Kurosawa"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which director had lengthy conversations with Kubrick on the phone but when asking Kubrick about his own movie-making secrets, Kubrick acted like he couldn't talk?",
        "options": ["Ingmar Bergman", "Federico Fellini", "Akira Kurosawa", "Andrei Tarkovsky"],
        "correctAnswer": "Federico Fellini"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which foreign director's films did Kubrick describe as unearthly and brilliant in his fan letter to the director?",
        "options": ["Ingmar Bergman", "Federico Fellini", "Akira Kurosawa", "Andrei Tarkovsky"],
        "correctAnswer": "Ingmar Bergman"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which actor is notorious for requiring the least amount of takes of Kubrick's collaborators?",
        "options": ["Jack Nicholson", "Matthew Modine", "Nicole Kidman", "R. Lee Emery"],
        "correctAnswer": "R. Lee Emery"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What film did Kubrick meet his wife Christiane on?",
        "options": ["The Killing", "Spartacus", "Paths of Glory", "Fear and Desire"],
        "correctAnswer": "Paths of Glory"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which of these was NOT a potential project for Stanley Kubrick?",
        "options": ["Napoleon", "Artificial Intelligence", "Aryan Papers", "Blade Runner"],
        "correctAnswer": "Blade Runner"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Which band requested that Kubrick direct them in a film?",
        "options": ["The Rolling Stones", "The Monkeys", "The Beatles", "Pink Floyd"],
        "correctAnswer": "The Beatles"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "What book did The Beatles want to adapt and have Kubrick direct?",
        "options": ["The Sun also Rises", "The Great Gatsby", "The Lord of the Rings", "1984"],
        "correctAnswer": "The Lord of the Rings"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Who acted in The Shining, A Clockwork Orange, and Barry Lyndon?",
        "options": ["Philip Stone", "Leon Vitali", "Steven Berkoff", "Patrick Magee"],
        "correctAnswer": "Philip Stone"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Who acted in Eyes Wide Shut and Barry Lyndon?",
        "options": ["Philip Stone", "Leon Vitali", "Steven Berkoff", "Patrick Magee"],
        "correctAnswer": "Leon Vitali"
    }, 
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Who in Stanley's family has appeared in 3 of his films?",
        "options": ["Vivian", "Christiane", "Anya", "Katherina"],
        "correctAnswer": "Vivian"
    }
]